export default  [

  {
    "category": "PowerPlatform",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What are the 4 components that are included in the Power Platform?",
    "correct_answer": "Power BI, Power Apps, Power Automate and Power Virtual Agents",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Power BI, Power Apps",
        "Power BI, Power Apps, Power Automatic",
        "Power BI, Power Apps, Power Automatic and Power Agents"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerPlatform",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is Power Platform used for?",
    "correct_answer": "low-code application development, workflow automation, AI bot development, and data analytics",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "low-code application development",
        "low-code application development, workflow automation",
        "low-code application development, AI bot development"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "SharePoint",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Is Power Platform SaaS or PaaS?",
    "correct_answer": "PaaS",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "SaaS",
        "No, it's IaaS",
        "It's just a library"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerPlatform",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What language is Power Platform?",
    "correct_answer": "Power Fx",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Power Function",
        "Power Language",
        "Power Code"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerPlatform",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Is Power Fx open source?",
    "correct_answer": "Yes",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "No, it's licensed.",
        "It depends if you are student.",
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerPlatform",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Can you explain what the Common Data Service is?",
    "correct_answer": "The Common Data Service is a cloud-based data service that allows applications to connect to common data sources.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The Common Data Service is a library to create a Restful API.",
        "The Common Data Service does not exists.",
        "The Common Data Service is still on the roadmap."
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerPlatform",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What are entities in PowerApps?",
    "correct_answer": "Entities in PowerApps are used to store and manage data.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Entities are interfaces within your PowerApp.",
        "Entities are visual widgets which you can drag into your viewport.",
        "Entities are used for caching mainly."
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerPlatform",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "When was the first version of PowerBI released?",
    "correct_answer": "2013",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2012",
        "2014",
        "2015"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerPlatform",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is the threshold limit of subsites in a site in SharePoint 2019?",
    "correct_answer": "2000",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2500",
        "1500",
        "3000"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerPlatform",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Office 365 is IaaS or SaaS or PaaS?",
    "correct_answer": "SaaS",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "PaaS",
        "IaaS",
        "It's just a program."
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "SharePoint",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What do you mean by MOSS?",
    "correct_answer": "MOSS refers to Microsoft Office SharePoint Server",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "MOSS refers to Microsoft Office Security Server",
        "MOSS refers to Microsoft Office SharePoint System",
        "MOSS refers to Microsoft Office SharePoint Service"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "SharePoint",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is the difference between SharePoint and OneDrive?",
    "correct_answer": "SharePoint stores business documents for a team in a Team site, OneDrive stores business documents for your own use.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "OneDrive stores business documents for a team in a Team site, SharePoint stores business documents for your own use.",
        "OneDrive is for non-business usage.",
        "SharePoint and OneDrive are the same thing."
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "SharePoint",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Can an event receiver be deployed through a SharePoint feature?",
    "correct_answer": "Yes",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "No",
        "Event receivers do not exist",
        "Yes, if deployed on a tuesday"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerPlatform",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Why is the Patch function used in canvas Power Apps?",
    "correct_answer": "Patch function is used to add or modify records in a data source.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Patch function is used to modify records in a data source.",
        "Patch function is used to modify the visual view.",
        "Patch function is not known in Power Apps"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": ".NET",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What does LINQ stands for?",
    "correct_answer": "Language Integrated Query",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Language Integration Query",
        "Lexical Integrated Query",
        "Language Integrated Qode"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "SharePoint",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is SSS in SharePoint?",
    "correct_answer": "Secure Store Service",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Security Store Service",
        "Safety Store Service",
        "Secure Store Stream"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "SharePoint",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is impersonation in SharePoint?",
    "correct_answer": "Something is executed in the context of a different identity.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Something is executed in the context of a different identity.",
        "A task to authenticate yourself against AAD.",
        "Impersonation is not possible in SharePoint."
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "SharePoint",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "How to make the site public in SharePoint?",
    "correct_answer": "To make it public, a user has to enable anonymous access for the entire site.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Sites are public by default, nothing to do here.",
        "It's not possible to make it public.",
        "Sites can only be made public for specific people."
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "SharePoint",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is CAML in SharePoint?",
    "correct_answer": "Collaborative Application Markup Language",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Collaborative Application Management Language",
        "Code Application Markup Language",
        "CollaborAtive Markup Language"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Viva",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is Microsoft Viva Learning?",
    "correct_answer": "Viva Learning is a centralized learning hub in Microsoft Teams that lets you seamlessly integrate learning and building skills into your day",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Viva is the next version and rebrading of Microsoft Teams.",
        "Microsoft Viva Learning does not exists.",
        "Microsoft Viva Learning is the new name for LinkedIn."
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Viva",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is a prerequisite for Microsoft Viva Learning?",
    "correct_answer": "Microsoft Teams deployed in your organization",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "You don't need anything, Microsoft Viva Learning is a stand-a-lone product.",
        "You need a Microsoft 365 learning license.",
        "You need a SharePoint Server 2020 installation."
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Teams",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is a Teams channel?",
    "correct_answer": "A virtual place to allow teammates to have focused conversations about specific topics.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A public channel that is accessible by every employee.",
        "The concept of a channel does not exists, it's a room.",
        "Teams channels are created by default, and you cannot customize them."
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Viva",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Is Microsoft Teams only accessible from the browser?",
    "correct_answer": "The Microsoft Teams app can be used on Windows, Mac, Linux (PWA), Android, & iOS.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The Microsoft Teams app can be downloaded for Windows only",
        "The Microsoft Teams app can be downloaded for Window and Mac.",
        "The Microsoft Teams app can be downloaded for Window, Android & iOS."
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Viva",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "How many languages does Microsoft Viva Learning support?",
    "correct_answer": "27",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "7",
        "17",
        "37"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Teams",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "When was Teams released?",
    "correct_answer": "2017",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2016",
        "2015",
        "2018"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Viva",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is not part of the Viva Suite License?",
    "correct_answer": "Viva Sales",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Viva Engage",
        "Viva Connects",
        "Viva Goals"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Teams",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "When will you need a Teams Room Pro license to use multiple sceens on MTR?",
    "correct_answer": "July, 1st 2023",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "July, 1st 2024",
        "December, 1st 2023",
        "December, 1st 2024"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Viva",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What was PowerBI based on?",
    "correct_answer": "All of the above",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Power Query",
        "Power Pivot",
        "Power View"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Viva",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "How is the engine called which sits on top Power Bi?",
    "correct_answer": "Vertipaq",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Unity engine",
        "PolyBase",
        "Vertipack"
      ]
  },{
    "category": "Chris",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which Github tool can detect vulnerabilities in the dependencies of your Github repository?",
    "correct_answer": "Dependabot",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Github copilot",
        "Github scanning",
        "Vulneracheck",
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Chris",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is Github Artifacts?",
    "correct_answer": "A way to store data produced by a workflow",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A cloud storage solution from Github",
        "A place to store source code",
        "A solution for an open issue",
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Chris",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is Github Actions?",
    "correct_answer": "A platform that allows you to automate CI/CD (Build, Test, Deployment), and react to other GitHub events.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A bot that helps you improve your DevOps Automation",
        "A tool that helps you take action on security issues inside your codebase.",
        "An AI pair programmer",
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Chris",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What tool can help you create a quick and consistent development environment?",
    "correct_answer": "GitHub Codespaces",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "GitHub Copilot",
        "GitHub Actions",
        "GitHub Container Registry",
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "GitHub secret scanning is available",
    "correct_answer": "on private repos with GitHub Advanced Security and public repos on github.com",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Only private repos on github.com",
        "GitHub Enterprise Server",
        "Only public repos on github.com"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Teams",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "In Mesh for Teams, your avatar has no __",
    "correct_answer": "Legs",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Eyebrows",
        "Arms",
        "Hair"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Teams",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "In Teams, OC stands for?",
    "correct_answer": "Operator Connect",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Office Center",
        "Operator Contract",
        "Operator Calling"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Teams",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What license does a Teams Phone device in the lobby requires to allow calling?",
    "correct_answer": "Common Area Phone License",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Shared Device License",
        "Phone Lobby License",
        "Reception Desk Phone License"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Teams",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "MTRoA means ...",
    "correct_answer": "Microsoft Teams Rooms on Android",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Microsoft Teams Rooms on Azure",
        "Microsoft Teams Rooms of Angels",
        "Microsoft Teams Rooms on Active"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Teams",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "In the near future, all Call Queues and Auto Attendants will need ...",
    "correct_answer": "Microsoft Teams Phone Resource Account license",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Microsoft Teams Phone System license",
        "Microsoft Teams Phone E3 license",
        "Microsoft Teams Virtual Phone license"
      ]
  }
]